stop being so hopeful
expect that most things are going to go
wrong married job holidays
kids look at the glass half empty and
then feel grateful whenever things
art and outcry catastrophe stop ranting
about how awful
other people are mister knowing people
are people interest anxious to see to
deepen
they didn't set out to hurt you just
under a lot of pressure think
death lot keeper Scala new table you
probably got about 400,000
laughable said stop thinking this
officer stupid
something for myself love looking
forward make Britain repentance to talk
with someone you don't spend enough time
you ask yourself what you really want an
anxious about
stop trying to make yourself happy it's
impossible concentrate and cheering up
you get yourself tested from I S S 240
miles above the earth
from this height lots of things that are
bothering you look for signs they should
always have been
through your phone off a cliff for a bit
so you can finally noticed
especially a partner and your mom give
up on the idea that we should be normal
the only normal people people you don't
know yet everyone is weird
its conclusion came